Adhan Nur

Portfolio | LinkedIn | adhamnur147@gmail.com | 07414139595

Summary

Detail-oriented analytical thinker offering sharp time management, organizational, and research skills. I am a recent graduate with a BSc (Hons) in Psychology with placement, seeking an entry-level data analysis position. With five years of experience working in hospitality, I have a track record of achieving corporate objectives while delivering outstanding services, resulting in high customer satisfaction. Additionally, I have experiences in the clinical and research fields in Psychology.

Skills

Technical Skills: Excel (Formulas, Pivot tables, XLOOKUP, conditional formatting & data cleaning)

SQL, Python, Tableau & Power BI. Plus basic HTML & CSS

Project Delivery, Continuous Improvement, SPSS software, and Qualtrics (data collection).

Education & Certifications

BSc (Hons) Psychology [with placement] Brunel University London Graduated 2021

Modules include:

Bio Psych (A), Statistics (B), & Clinical Psychology (B)

Google Data Analytics Professional CertificateCourseraSeptember 2022Mobile MarketingGoogle Digital GarageJanuary 2022Fundamentals of Digital MarketingGoogle Digital GarageJanuary 2022Psychological First AidCourseraFebruary 2021

Work Experience

Assistant Supervisor Bandar Supermarket April 2022 - Current

Working at an independent family-run supermarket, butcher shop and cafe.

- Trained staff on health and safety, till use & cashing out.
- Managed incoming deliveries and completed quality control over inventory.
- Completed deliveries to our customers and carried out customer satisfaction reviews.
- > Deputised for store manager on several occasions and ensured the store is maintained at all times.
- Produced ad hoc reports on product sales and income via Excel.

Customer Service Assistant

M&S

August 2021 - Current

- Organised, labelled & processed over 100 items daily accommodating constantly changing shipping schedules & delivery times
- Demonstrated leadership and management abilities
- ➤ Contribute to store sales & cost control
- > Performed daily quality checks to ensure damaged items were recorded and removed
- Understand customer needs & spot selling opportunities
- > Cashing out tills & handling thousands of pounds of cash daily and accurately recording.

Team Member StarPret A MangerNov 2018 – Jan 2020Hot Chef(Promotion)Jan 2020 –

August 2020

- Worked with a group of 5 team members to improve daily sales and breaking area records for the highest gross income on the weekend, by utilizing key performance indicators for hourly & weekly food sales.
- Responsible for producing the highest quality product and trained new colleagues on key aspects of the job.
- Received additional training in Health & Safety (including First Aid), COSHH handling as well as Barista training.

> Contributed ideas into multiple projects in the Centre for Culture and Evolution with a primary focus on the 'Infidelity Motivation' study.

> Conducted data analysis (SPSS, Qualtrics & Excel), designed experiments (via Gorilla), prepared ethics applications, edited research proposals, and contributed to research papers.

Assistant Vocational Teaching Officer Bank Life Skills Practitioner

OPTIONS West London Community College Au

College Aug 2018 -Dec 2018 May 2019 – Jan 21 (Periodically)

Worked one-on-one with adults who are living with autism alongside, learning disability, depression, anxiety, muscle dystrophy, fragile X and reduced communication skills. I assisted the speech and language therapist in implementing therapeutic techniques.

- Basic Makaton (simplified sign language)
- Leading life skills sessions (including maths and road safety)
- > Risk management
- Planning
- Daily/Monthly evaluation of progress

During this time, I further enhanced my skills by completing a 'Care Certificate Standard Level 1'